Guide to the Association of Fundraising Professionals Records, Western Pennsylvania Chapter, 1980-2005 AIS.2003.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Fund Raising Day, 1987-2005; IV.
  - Allegheny County, PA recognizes Fund Raising Day, April 7, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Regional Philanthropy Day Conference, February 15, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Fund Raising Day, February 7-8, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Fund Raising Day, February 20, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Fund Raising Day, May 9-10, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Fund Raising Day, April 18, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 31-32)
  - Fund Raising Day, April 9, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 33-34)
  - Fund Raising Day, April 8, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Fund Raising Day, April 8, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 01-02)
- NSFRE Conference and National Assembly Materials, 1986-1996; V.
  These files contain brochures for the International Conference on Fund Raising and papers pertaining to the National Assemblies of the NSFRE. Also included in some files are papers regarding chapter scholarships for individuals to attend the International Conference.
  - International Conference of Fund Raising, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - International Conference of Fund Raising, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - International Conference of Fund Raising, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - International Conference of Fund Raising, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - International Conference of Fund Raising, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - International Conference of Fund Raising, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - International Conference of Fund Raising, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - International Conference of Fund Raising, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - International Conference of Fund Raising, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - International Conference of Fund Raising, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - NSFRE National Assembly, March 1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NSFRE National Assembly, November 1992 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NSFRE National Assembly, February 1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - NSFRE National Assembly, November 1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Chapter and National Publications, 1982-2005; VI.
  These files contain the NSFRE International Newsletters and the NSFRE - WPA Newsletters. In 2001 the name of the organization changed from the National Association of Fund Raising Executives to the Association of Fundraising Professionals. This is evidenced by the changing of the newsletter title in 2001.
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletter, October 1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - NSFRE - WPA Newsletters, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - AFP - WPA Newsletters, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - AFP - WPA Newsletters, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - AFP - WPA Newsletters, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - AFP - WPA Newsletters, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - AFP - WPA Newsletters, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - NSFRE Newsletters, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Media, VII.
  These files contain photos from different foundational meetings, such as National Philanthropy Day and Fund Raising Day. Also, there are two 7 ½ ips that contain public service announcements for National Philanthropy Day 1990 and 1991. There is one U-matic video-tape that contains two public service announcements for National Philanthropy Day 1991.
  - National Philanthropy Day Photos, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - National Philanthropy Day Photos, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - NSFRE Youth Program, 1992 -1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Unknown Event (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Trustee Pete and Sybil Veeder, Gishie and Arthur Scully; Catholic Charities Check; Award Recipient (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Earl Gadbery, John G Rangos Sr., Frank B. Fuhrer Jr. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Unknown Couple (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Sandie Fauriol; Fund Raising Day Speaker, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Robert E. Eberly (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ellen Walton (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Ed McMahon and Myron Berezin at National Philanthropy Day, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dolly Ellenberg, President; Janet C. Emery, CFRE (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - George Omiros (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Fund Raising Day, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Fund Raising Day, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Transparency of Pittsburgh City Skyline (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Students Helping Others Representatives, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - U-matic video of PSA's for National Philanthropy Day, 1991 (Box 8, Item 1)
  - 7 ½ ips of PSA for National Philanthropy Day, 1990 (Box 8, Item 2)
  - 7 ½ ips of PSA for National Philanthropy Day, 1991 (Box 8, Item 3)